itickets.com 2018-12-29

# Privacy Policy | iTickets

**Effective June 1, 1999 (last updated April 22, 2016)**

**iTickets Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy discloses how we collect, protect, use and share information gathered about you both online and offline. It includes our websites, apps, walk-up box offices, phone or email interactions.

**What type of information is iTickets collecting, and how is it being collecting?**

The majority of products and services on our sites are offered without our collecting any personally identifiable information from you. You can surf iTickets's Web sites and view much of our content anonymously. (For instance, you can search events without giving out any personally identifiable information.)

**Information You Provide**

There are a few activities on our sites where the collection of personally identifiable information is necessary. Those activities include things like entering a contest or sweepstakes, making a purchase, or contacting us. When personally identifiable information is collected, you will know because you will have to fill out a form. For most activities, we collect only your name, e-mail address, birth date, gender, and zip code. When you make a purchase, we also collect your street and billing addresses, your phone number, and credit card information. Depending on what you purchase, we may also need to collect other personal information, like your clothing size. We may also collect information you post in a public space on our website or on a third-party social media site.

When visiting our website, we may collect information about the browser you’re using. We may also look at what site you came from, or what site you visit when you leave us. We might also collect the type of device you are using and the version of the operating system your device is running. If you use iTickets mobile app, we will collect your GPS location or your device's unique identifier. We may also look at how often you use the app and where you downloaded it.

**Information Collected from You with Technology**

iTickets sites collect some information about you using tracking tools like browser cookies and web beacons. For instance, when you come to our site your IP address is collected so that we know where to send information you are requesting. An IP address is often associated with the place from which you enter the **internet** like your ISP (internet service provider), your company, or your university. This information is not personally identifiable. iTickets sites use information collected through technology to make our sites more interesting and useful to you. This includes helping advertisers on our site design advertisements of interests to our guests. We normally don't combine this type of information with personally identifiable information. However, we will combine this information with personally identifiable information to identify a visitor in order to enforce compliance with our house rules or terms of service or to protect our service, site, guests, or others.

**What are cookies, and how does iTickets use them?**

Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site sends to your computer while you are viewing the Web site. These pieces of information allow the Web site to remember important information that will make your visit of that site more useful. iTickets and other **internet** companies use cookies for a variety of purposes. For instance, iTickets uses cookies to remember and process the items in your shopping cart.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many iTickets features that make your Web experience more efficient -- like the features mentioned above -- and some of our services will not function properly.

**How does iTickets use the personally identifiable information that has been collected?**

iTickets uses personally identifiable information in a limited number of ways. We use the information to complete transactions. For instance, if you purchase a ticket on iTickets, we use your information to process your order, or if you contact us for help we will use the information to contact you. We use information collected to notify you if you've won a game or contest. Information we collect is used to send you e-mail updates and newsletters about our sites. We also use the information you provide to send you iTickets e-mail promotions and special offers from our third-party sponsors.

We provide content to third-party promoters that ticket their events via our site. This content is shared on the ticket buyer's behalf. This allows ticket buyers to receive any last minute updates that pertain to the event they are attending. Third party promoters may also send you other special promotions they offer, or information on future events, and we will share it only with that specific third-party promoter.

**Does iTickets share information with companies or other organizations that are not part of the iTickets family of sites?**

One of the most valuable assets of our business is you. We will not give or sell your information. However, if there is a value for our guests, we will share your information or send you messages on behalf of another company as described below. We will also share information for security reasons.

**Companies That Are "Standing in the Shoes" of iTickets**

Sometimes we hire companies to help us deliver products or services, like a shipping company that delivers a package. In those instances, we need to share your information with them. These companies are basically "standing in the shoes" of iTickets, and they are allowed to use the information only to deliver the product or service.

**Companies Offering Promotions, Products, or Services**

On occasion, we offer promotions -- like sweepstakes or free subscriptions in conjunction with a sponsor. We will share your information with the sponsors if they need it to send you a product, such as a CD or T-shirt. In addition, iTickets occasionally sends e-mail promotions out to our guests on behalf of third-party sponsors. In this instance, we don't share your name with the third party -- we do the mailing for them.

**Content Partners**

On some of our sites, we provide content that is created by a third-party partner Web site. For instance, we provide search engines to third parties. In some instances the third-party sites will collect information in order to facilitate the transaction or to make the use of their content more productive and efficient. In these circumstances the information collected is shared between iTickets and our third-party sponsors.

**Third-Party Advertisers and Network Advertisers**

To help increase privacy protections for our guests, iTickets allows advertising on our sites from only those companies that have their own privacy policy. Once you've clicked on an advertisement and have left iTickets sites, our privacy policy no longer applies. You must read the privacy policy of the advertiser to see how your personal information will be handled on their site. We are not responsible for third party sites.

In addition, many business advertisements are managed and placed on our site by third-party companies. These companies are called "network advertisers." Network advertisers collect non-personally identifiable information when you click on or scan one of their banner advertisements. The information is collected using technology, so you may not realize it's being collected. The network advertisers collect this information so that they can show you ads that are more relevant and interesting to you.

**Purchase or Sale of Businesses**

Online business is constantly changing and evolving rapidly. As iTickets continually looks for ways to improve our business, we may buy or sell a company. If we buy or sell a business, the names collected will likely be transferred as a part of the sale. Information about registrants will be used in the aggregate. However, if we buy a business, we will honor the requests that customers made of that business regarding e-mail communications. In the event that we sell a business, we will do everything in our power to ensure that the e-mail communications requests you made of us are honored.

**Organizations That Help Protect the Security and Safety of Our Guests and Our Sites**

We will give out personal information as required by law, for example, to comply with a court order or subpoena; to enforce our Terms of Service, or site or game rules; or to protect the safety and security of guests and our sites.

**What choices do I have about iTickets collecting, using, and sharing my information?**

It is possible for you to use much of our site without giving us any personally identifiable information. When you do register with us or give us personally identifiable information, you will have an opportunity at the time we collect your information -- to limit e-mail communications from iTickets and from our third-party partners. You can request at any time that iTickets not send future e-mail to you by unsubscribing. Also, as mentioned above, there are ways to limit the information collected through technology -- though some of our features won't work if you decide to do this.

**What type of security does iTickets provide?**

iTickets takes technical, contractual, administrative, and physical security steps to protect all visitors' information. The standard security measures we use will depend on the type of information collected. When you provide credit card information, we use secure socket layer (SSL) encryption to protect it. However, the Internet is not 100% secure. We cannot promise that your use of our sites will be completely safe.

We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet. There are some things that you can do to help protect the security of your information as well. For instance, never give out your Password, since this is what is used to access all of your account information. Also, remember to sign out of your account and close your browser window when you finish surfing the Web, so that other people using the same computer won't have access to your information. If you think that an unauthorized account has been created using your name, contact us immediately.
